早上好
Good morning.
你居然起来了
I'm surprised you're up,
昨晚你那么晚才从洛杉矶回来呢
given how late you got in from L.A. last night.
我想趁你上班之前跟你
Well, I thought we could play a little catch up
说说情况
before you got off to work.
我洗耳恭听
I'm all ears.
-谢谢  -小心
- Thanks. - Careful.
-我今早调得比较浓  -好
- I made it a little strong this morning. - Okay.
嗯  连死人都能惊醒了
Yes, that will wake the dead.
那样你的工作就轻松多了
Certainly make your job a lot easier.
问一次话
One interview,
"是他杀了我"  结案
"He's the guy who killed me," case closed.
卡塞尔  我猜你发现了
Castle, I'm guessing that you found out
关于你失忆时间的事
something about your missing time,
这就是你想跟我说的吧
and that's what you want to catch up with me on.
是的
Uh... Uh, yeah.
是这样
Actually, yeah, I did. Um...
但我们要不要先吃饭
But I was thinking how about we eat first?
那么糟糕啊
That bad?
敲敲
Knock-knock.
你穿好了吗
Are you decent?
母亲
Mother!
欢迎回家  亲爱的
Welcome home, darling.
真是意外之喜
Oh, what a pleasant surprise.
你...怎么不先打个电话
You know, you... you could've... could've called first.
我怕你想多睡会儿  不想打扰你
I didn't want to disturb you in case you wanted to sleep in.
亲爱的
Oh, darling.
我想偷偷溜进来
I thought I would just sneak in
给我儿子做早餐
and make my boy a little breakfast.
讨厌
Oh, well, phooey.
你抢先了
You beat me to it.
-是啊  -有人要来吗
- Yeah, I... Well... - You expecting someone?
就是习惯了
Oh, just old habit.
你真是专程来给我做早餐的吗
So, uh, did you really come just to make me breakfast?
这听上去怎么不像你呢
Because that does not sound like you.
其实
Oh, pishposh. Actually,
我刚拿到了我新书的预览本
I just got an advanced copy of my book
我想让你看看
that I wanted you to see.
《主动忠告》  玛莎·罗杰斯著
Unsolicited Advice by Martha Rodgers.
妈妈  我好为你骄傲
Mother, I'm so proud of you!
谢谢  看看致部分
Oh, thank you. Read the dedication.
"致理查德
"For Richard.
要不是你总在人生中犯错
Without your constant stumbles in life,
我也不会想出这本书里的忠告"
the advice in this book would not have been possible."
总是犯错
Constant stumbles?
别把重点转移到你身上
Let's not make this about you.
我...
It...
稍等
One second.
你在哪
Hey, where are you?
走廊
Hallway.
我从卧室溜出来了
I, uh, snuck out through the bedroom.
差点成了最大的讽刺
That would be the height of irony, huh?
成功对洛克塞特隐瞒了我们的恋情
Manage to successfully hide our relationship from LokSat
却被你妈妈发现了
only to get outed by your mom.
要不要我午饭时溜回来
Look, do you want me to sneak back at lunch
好跟你谈谈你的发现
so we can talk about what you found?
不用
No, no. Okay.
我们今晚见吧
I... I'll see you tonight.
好
Okay.
我得挂了
Listen, I got to go.
我爱你
I love you.
再见
Bye.
我想说
So, I just wanted to say...
我是贝克特
This is Beckett.
好了  各位  什么情况
All right, guys. What do we got?
目前被害人身份不明
Right now, our victim is a John Doe.
他身上没有电话或身份证
There's no phone or I.D. on the victim,
但我们扫描了他的指纹  正在搜寻
but we scanned his prints and we're running them now.
从血迹来看  他应该是在拐角处
From the blood trail, looks like he was shot
中了枪  然后在这里倒下
around the corner and collapsed here.
好  我还是不明白
Okay, I'm still not sure
为什么非要叫警监过来
why you needed the captain to come down.
被害人是背后中枪
Our victim was shot in the back.
他几分钟内就失血致死
He bled out within a few minutes,
然后凶手耗费时间  不惜冒险
then the killer took the time and the risk
把子弹割了出来
to cut out the bullet.
显然  凶手担心
Obviously, our killer was worried
弹道报告会暴露他的身份
that ballistics would lead back to him.
所以这把枪在系统中
Which means the gun's already in the system.
知道死亡时间了吗
Do you have a time of death?
9点到午夜之间
9:00 and midnight.
指纹有匹配
Got a hit on the fingerprint match.
被害人叫丹尼尔·巴多
Our victim's name is Daniel Bardot.
是纽约警局学院的学员
He's a Recruit Officer at the NYPD Academy.
他是我们自己人
He's one of us.
我们拿到了巴多的手机记录
We got Bardot's phone records.
但是他手机的定位系统关掉了
Unfortunately, the GPS was turned off on his cell.
我们尚不知道他在那一带做什么
We still don't know what he was doing in that neighborhood.
电话呢
What about calls?
他最后打的一通电话是5:30给中城区一家律所
Last call he made was at 5:30 to a law firm in midtown.
只通话了一分钟
It only lasted a minute.
维克拉姆正在核查
Vikram's checking it out.
我奶奶比你们仨加起来都强壮
My granny's stronger than all three of you guys combined!
-回忆起来啥了吗  哥们  -你得有决心
- Bad flashbacks, bro? - You got to want it!
-这里干啥都要做俯卧撑  -快点
- Pushups were the answer to everything around this place. - Come on!
警察工作可不仅仅是力气和耐力
Police work is more than just strength and endurance.
还需要脑子的
It's about intellectual rigor.
得了  也没那么糟
Oh, come on, you guys. It wasn't all that bad here.
学院全明星如是说
Says the Academy All-Star.
看啊  贝克特学员
Oh, look. Recruit Officer Beckett.
贝克特学员
Recruit Officer Beckett.
又是贝克特学员
我去跟学院局长了解情况了
I'm gonna go download with the Academy Commissioner.
你们去巴多的寝室
You guys head over to Bardot's dorm room.
这里肯定有指向他凶手的线索
There's got to be a clue here as to who his killer is.
副局长马龙
Hi, Deputy Commissioner Malone.
我是凯特·贝克特警监
I'm Captain Kate Beckett.
警监  很高兴终于见到你了
Captain, nice to finally meet you.
你在这里是个传奇
You're a bit of a legend around these parts.
我五年前到的时候  新生们
Recruits have been gunning for your records
就一直想打破你的纪录
since I got here five years ago.
目前还没人看到希望呢
So far, no one's gotten close.
他们会的
Yeah, well, they will.
所有纪录总有被打破的时候
Every record falls in the end.
这是巴多的档案
Here's Bardot's file.
我已经安排他的教官奥蒂兹警长
I've assigned his instructor, Sergeant Ortiz,
做你的联络人
to be your liaison.
你认识奥蒂兹警长吗
You know Sergeant Ortiz?
是的
Yeah, I do.
他是我当年的教官
He was my instructor when I was here.
他的严厉管教是
His tough love is the reason
我的名字能挂在外面的原因
my name's on all of those plaques out there.
请进  警长
Come in, Sergeant.
谢谢  长官
Thank you, sir.
贝克特警监
Captain Beckett.
很高兴能见到你  警长
It's so good to see you, Sergeant.
跟我说说丹尼尔·巴多
So, what can you tell me about Daniel Bardot?
他是个值得钦佩的孩子
He was an admirable kid.
他小时候很不容易
Got a rough start in life.
九岁的时候父母在抢劫中被杀
His parents were killed in a robbery when he was nine.
在狩猎点区长大  这种事不足为奇
Not surprising when you grow up in Hunts Point.
爱尔兰黑帮的后院
The Irish Mafia's backyard.
那个肮脏的熔炉里
There's not a lot of good cops
可没走出来很多好警察
coming out of that dirty furnace.
可不是
Don't have to tell me.
我曾跟
I went toe-to-toe
那个"幸运杰克"弗拉纳根针锋相对
with that 'hood "Lucky Jack" Flanagan
那是早在我教你之前了
long before I was teaching you.
一直没能给那家伙定罪
Never could make a charge stick on that guy.
巴多能一直走到这里来
Bardot must have had a lot of fortitude
一定很刚毅啊
to make it all the way over here.
他决心十足
He was definitely driven.
但他也常常
But he also had a tendency
被情绪左右
to let emotion get the best of him.
他会不假思索地冲动行事
He'd rush into situations without thinking,
这几天来更加严重了
and it had gotten worse in the last few days.
什么意思
What do you mean?
他总在一项他一般很拿手的操练中失手
He kept fumbling a tactical drill he usually aced,
所以我单独质问了他
so I pulled him aside and confronted him.
他说他在私人生活中搞砸了什么事
He said he'd screwed something up in his personal life.
不知道该如何是好
He didn't know what to do.
我叫他勇敢起来  纠正错误
I told him to cowboy up, set it right.
现在我觉得他可能正是因此而死
And now I'm thinking he died trying to do just that.
你没把洛杉矶的事告诉凯特吗
You didn't tell Kate what happened in Los Angeles?
-你临阵退缩了  -我才没有
- You chickened out. - I did not chicken out, all right?
我是被打断了
I was interrupted.
现在我在想这或许是宇宙给我的暗示
Now I'm wondering whether it was a sign from the universe.
什么
What?
宇宙叫你妈妈来告诉你什么
The universe sent your mother to tell you what?
听从我自己的建议
To take my own advice.
我清除咱们的记忆是有原因的
I am erasing our mind for a reason...
为了保护凯特
to protect Kate.
好了  够了
Okay. Enough.
去跟你妻子谈谈
Go and talk to your wife.
如果我没有抹去我的记忆
If I hadn't wiped my memory,
贝克特在总检察长办公室的朋友或许就不会死
Beckett's friends at the A.G.'s office might still be alive.
如果她不肯原谅我呢
What if she can't forgive me?
那不是你能做的决定  里克
That decision's not yours to make, Rick.
搞什么  巴多的房间跟我当年的比大好多
What? Bardot's room is huge compared to the one I lived in.
那简直是个储物间
Thing was barely a closet.
我从未在校园里住过
Yeah, I never really bunked on campus.
我当兵时受够了住寝室
I got enough of communal living when I was in the army.
而且  又不能把
And besides, you can't really bring
一群警察粉带回寝室
a minage of cop groupies home to a dorm room.
你们在这里做什么
What are you doing in here?
我们在调查凶案  你是谁
We're investigating a homicide. Who are you?
蕾切尔·戴克学员
Recruit Officer Rachel Decker.
你认识丹尼尔·巴多吗
Did you know Daniel Bardot?
是的  长官  他是我们学员队的
Yes, sir. He was in my training company.
你知道他昨晚去哪了吗
You know what he was doing last night?
不  长官  我们邀请他一同来  但他回绝了
No, sir. We invited him to go out with us, but he begged off.
长官  如果我能协助你们的调查
Sir, if there's any way I can help with this investigation,
我愿加入
I want in.
你忘记自己的身份了吧  戴克
You forget your place, Decker?
你连个巡警都不是
You're not even a lowly uniform.
你能帮上这些了不起的警探什么忙
What could you possibly offer these distinguished detectives?
内情
Insight.
你和巴多学员一同训练吗
Did you train alongside Officer Bardot?
是的  长官
Yes, ma'am.
那么你们一定同心
So you forged a bond with him
对付邪恶的奥蒂兹警长吧
against the evil Sergeant Ortiz,
那么你肯定有高层不了解的关于
which means you have information on Bardot
巴多的情报
that his higher-ups do not.
-是不是  学员  -是
- Is that correct, recruit? - Yes.
那告诉我  他遇到什么麻烦了
So then tell me, what was he struggling with?
他需要补救什么事
What did he need to set right?
我不知道
I don't know.
抱歉
Sorry.
真会给上级留下好印象  戴克
Way to face-plant in front of a superior, Decker.
这位是布克特警监
This is Captain Beckett.
警监  我
Captain, I...
你可以解散了  学员
You're dismissed, recruit.
-太严厉了吧  -不会
- That was a little harsh, don't you think? - I do not.
戴克就需要知道自己的轻重
Being put in her place is exactly what Decker needs.
她挺厉害的
She's the real deal.
等她离开时  她的名字或许能
Her name could very well be on all your trophies
刻上所有你拿过的奖杯
by the time she's done here.
但她急需学学什么是谦虚
But she desperately needs to learn a little humility.
蕾妮  尸检有发现吗
Lanie, you find anything in the autopsy?
有的
I did.
子弹击中肋骨时碎了
The bullet broke up when it hit a rib.
凶手没能取走所有碎片
Bardot's killer didn't get all the pieces.
我从一颗肾脏中取出了一小块
I managed to pull a small fragment from a kidney.
并匹配到弹道了
I got a ballistics match.
开枪的9毫米口径手枪的确在数据库中
The 9mm that fired it is in the database.
凯特  是纽约警局的枪
Kate, it's NYPD...
登记在学院名下
registered to the Academy.
凶器从巴多的学员队  38号学员队的
The murder weapon is missing from the weapons cage
武器箱失窃了
assigned to Bardot's company, Company 38.
监控安全柜的锁被撬
Lock on the CCTV security closet was jimmied open.
昨晚7:30到7:35之间  有人关掉了
Someone killed the security cameras in the weapons room
武器室的监控
7:30 and 7:35 last night.
那时  楼内大部分是学员
At that hour, it's mainly recruits who are left in the building.
教职工都住在校外
All faculty resides off-campus.
只有38号学员队的成员
And only members of Company 38
能够打开那个武器箱
have access to that weapons cage.
那么凶手是巴多的同班学员
So our killer is one of Bardot's fellow recruits.
14个嫌疑人
14 suspects
同吃  同喝  同睡  一同接受警察培训
who eat, drink, and sleep police training and techniques...
警监到
Captain on deck!
已经花了数月时间学习我们如何抓凶手
...who have spent months learning how we catch killers...
所以他们都有策划凶杀的能力
...which makes them uniquely equipped to plan a murder.
我们得用上所有招数
So we are gonna have to use every trick in the book
来找出是谁杀了丹尼尔·巴多
to uncover who killed Daniel Bardot.
稍息  各位学员  请坐
At ease, officers. Take a seat.
38号学员队
Company 38,
这位是12分局的贝克特警监
this is Captain Beckett of the 12th Precinct.
因为昨晚的悲剧事件
Because of last night's tragic event,
她今天将作为我们的特邀教官
she will be joining us today as a special guest instructor.
放尊重点  否则我踢你们屁股
Respect her, or your ass will meet my boot.
多谢  警长
Thank you, Sergeant.
首先  我向大家保证
First of all, let me assure you
我已经派了最好的纽约警局警探
that I have the best NYPD detectives
调查巴多学员的案子
looking into Officer Bardot's murder.
虽说如此  你们不会是最后一次
That being said, this is not going to be the last time
经历失去同事的痛苦
that you lose one of your coworkers.
这就是我们工作的现实情况
That is a reality of this job.
你们会想
The temptation
在困境中保持从容
is going to be to remain stoic in the face of adversity,
控制情绪  不显露软弱
to lock up your emotions so as not to appear weak.
那是个错误
That is a mistake.
无论如何要避免那么做
Avoid that temptation at all costs.
相信我
Trust me.
我曾走上过那条路
I have been at the edge of that map,
尽头是洪水猛兽
and monsters lie there.
环顾四周
Now look around.
这是你们的队伍
This is your team.
没人会比坐在你身边的
No one is gonna understand what you are feeling
男男女女更了解你们的感受
better than the woman or man sitting next to you,
所以  利用这一点
so use them.
钱伯斯学员
Officer Chambers.
我很遗憾你失去了同班学员
I'm very sorry about the loss of your fellow recruit.
你有什么感受
How do you feel?
这个城市失去了一个好警察  长官
The city lost a great cop, ma'am.
我们都应该
We should all aspire
立志成为他那样的正义守护者
to be a guardian of justice like he was.
这是给《邮报》的公关说辞吗
Is that a PR statement for the Post?
你们的一位兄弟被人枪杀
One of your brothers was gunned down.
我问的是你的感受
I asked you how you felt.
我们生气  警监
We feel pissed off, Captain.
是的  让我们出去
Yeah, set us loose.
让我们找到杀了他的混蛋
Let us track down the son of a bitch who did this.
戴克学员已经提出
Well, Officer Decker already volunteered her services
想帮忙了
for that very role.
我现在依然愿意  警监
The offer still stands, Captain.
老实说  我做警察
And frankly, I didn't become a cop
不是为了体会感受
to get in touch with my feelings.
我来这儿是因为这世上有坏人
I'm here because bad people exist in the world.
我等不及去
And I can't wait to start
把他们关进监狱  他们该去的地方
putting them in prison where they belong.
好啊  准备训练
All right. Get ready for a training session.
我刚查了大门记录
I just checked the front gate log.
巴多被杀的时候
10 of the recruits were off-campus
有10名学员离校
at the time of Bardot's murder.
好吧  他们三人有一样的手戳
All right. Well, these three all have the same hand stamp.
街对面的俱乐部
The club across the street
挂着昨晚卡拉OK的招牌
had a sign from last night offering karaoke.
我会让我的警探拿他们的照片去那边问问
So I'm gonna have my detectives run these photos over there,
但我猜他们会有不在场证明
but I'm guessing they're gonna alibi out.
那么剩他们七个了
Leaving these seven.
如果传出去
You know, if word gets out
这些学员都是嫌疑人
that these recruits are suspects,
他们今后都甩不掉的
it'll haunt their careers.
就算最终证实他们无罪
Even if proved innocent.
那我们得守住秘密
Well, then we need to keep it to a tight circle.
接下来怎么办
So what's the next move?
我觉得可以认定
Well, I think it's a safe bet
如果他们七个中有人杀了巴多
that if one of these seven killed Bardot,
他们应该是第一次杀人
it was their first murder.
除非他们完全是精神变态
And unless they're a complete psychopath...
而精神评估早会显示出这一点的
which the psych eval would have revealed...
那么此人肯定经历了漫长痛苦的一夜
then they spent a long, dark night of the soul,
回顾枪的后坐力
reliving the recoil of the gun
和用刀切割巴多的尸体
and the knife cutting into Bardot's body
挖子弹的时刻
to get that bullet out.
什么意思
Meaning what?
此人现在肯定很焦躁
Meaning they're on a razor's edge.
我要让他们做高压模拟
And I want to put them in a high-stress simulation
看他们开枪的样子
and watch them shoot a gun.
洛佩兹  高田  你们上
Lopez, Takata, you're up.
看  迟疑  怎么回事
There. That pause. What is that?
抱歉了  但是这对高田是常事
Hate to break it to you, but that's normal for Takata.
他就是出手慢  我改不过来
Guy's got a hitch in his giddy-up I cannot cure.
戴克  钱伯斯  你们上
Decker, Chambers, you're up.
戴克呢
What about Decker?
其他学员似乎不太喜欢她
The other recruits don't seem to like her.
学员都不喜欢戴克
Every recruit's got a problem with Decker.
她特别专注  非常好胜
She's ultra-focused, competitive as hell,
而且对所有人心墙高筑
and walled off from everyone.
就像你当年
Kind of like you were.
等等
Hey, wait a second.
巴多的战术装备
Bardot's tactical gear,
我们没在他的寝室找到
we didn't find it in his dorm room.
是的  我们有柜子  让他们放在这里
No, we put lockers in so they could keep it here.
-哪个柜子是巴多的  -7号
- And which locker is Bardot's? - Seven.
这是凯特·贝克特著名的直觉时刻吗
Am I witnessing one of Kate Beckett's famous hunches?
实验室没能从蓝贴纸上提取到指纹
The lab couldn't pull any prints off that blue index card.
已经让笔迹专家
Got our handwriting expert
跟其他嫌疑人的笔迹样本作对比了
comparing against samples from the other suspects,
但由于字体方方正正  他并不乐观
but he's not optimistic given the block letters.
-是贝克特吗  -是
- Is that Beckett? - Yeah.
我跟她说两句  贝克特
Let me holler at her. Beckett.
记得巴多死的那天给中城区的
Hey, you remember that phone call that Bardot made
律所打的那通电话吗
to that midtown law firm on the day he died?
嗯  我去了一趟  但没人记得那通电话
Yeah, I went over there. Only nobody remembers the call.
没有更多线索  这似乎查不下去了
So without more to go on, it looks like a dead end.
有消息我再告诉你
Yeah, I'll keep you posted.
贝克特不在
Beckett's not here.
她去警局学院查一宗要案了
She's at the Police Academy working a high-profile murder.
一位学员被杀了
One of the recruit officers was killed.
要杀到家门口了  他们是嫌犯吗
That's a little close to home. These the suspects?
是啊  又有三位学员证实了不在场证明
Yeah, and three more recruits just alibi'd out.
被害人是被同班学员杀的吗
Your victim was killed by a fellow recruit?
看来是如此
Appears so.
据传这四个在凶案发生时
And word is these four were watching the fights
在当地一家拳击馆看比赛
at a local boxing gym at the time of the murder,
但这个不在场证明不是很可靠
but that alibi's soft.
刚跟风化组的利兹通过话
Hey, just spoke with Liz from Vice.
拳击馆是非法激素的
The boxing gym is a notorious hotspot
出名热点地区
for illegal steroids.
据传有位教练在
Rumor has it that one of the trainers
向学院的一个警察贩毒
was dealing to a cop at the Academy.
那么被害人巴多是撞上了一个黑警
So the victim, Bardot, stumbled onto a dirty cop.
那就不怪有人写威胁便条了
Well, that would explain the threatening note.
死人不会乱说话
"Dead men tell no tales."
但巴多不肯放弃
But Bardot wouldn't back down,
于是那警察就杀了他
so the cop kills him.
那个贩毒的教练叫什么
What was the name of the trainer that was dealing?
亚瑟·斯廷森
Arthur Stinson,
你今天不走运
today's not your lucky day.
其实简直是霉运日
It's actually the complete opposite of your lucky day.
听着  我不知道别人说了什么
Look, man. I don't know what people been telling you,
但我不贩毒
but I don't sell drugs.
是吗  因为他们
Oh, really? 'Cause that's exactly
就是这么说的
what they've been telling us.
我们在你柜子
And the stash that we found
虚底下面发现的毒品证实了这一点
hidden in the false bottom of your locker confirms it.
这么办吧
So, here's the deal.
我们在地检官面前为你美言
We say nice things about you to the D.A.,
或许帮你争取个缓刑
maybe get you a suspended sentence
但你得把你学院里的那个买家
if you give up that cop you've been dealing to
告诉我们
at the Academy.
我不能
But I can't.
那我们没什么好说的了
Well, I guess we're done here, then.
替我们跟陪审团打招呼
Say hi to the jury for us.
我们根本没见过
I-I can't because we've never met.
听着
All right? Look.
那个警察把钱放进储物柜
The cop puts cash in the locker.
我去拿  再留下毒品  就是这样
I pick it up, I leave the drugs. That's it.
你怎么知道
So how do you know that
你是在跟警察交易
you're dealing to a police officer?
买家从来只安排在
The buyer only arranges pickups
"警民一家亲"夜进行交易
on "Police Appreciation" nights.
纽约警局不必交入场费
The NYPD doesn't pay a cover,
所以拳击馆里挤满了警察
the gym's crawling with cops.
买家如何联系你
How's the buyer contact you?
往我的储物柜里塞一张贴纸
They shove an index card in my locker.
上面写好什么时候交货
Note says when they want delivery.
等等  蓝色贴纸吗
Hold on. A blue index card?
是的
Yeah.
我知道贝克特要如何炸出凶手了
I think I know how Beckett can smoke out our killer.
审讯嫌疑人的重点
The thing about interviewing a suspect is
是找到合适自己的办法
you have to find what works for you...
你的个人风格
your own personal style.
有些人喜欢红脸白脸双簧
Now, some people like good cop/bad cop.
也有人喜欢白脸更白脸的搭配
Others like bad cop/worse cop.
但只采取一种方式是不对的
But choosing just one method is a mistake.
每个嫌犯都不一样
Every suspect is different.
有时候得等到对方开口你才知道
And sometimes you don't know how you're gonna go at them
该采取何种方式
until they start talking
因为审讯只有一次机会
because you only get one shot in interrogation,
如果你搞砸  凶手就可能逍遥法外
and if you screw it up, a killer might walk free.
所以  我想试验一下
So, I want to try something.
我需要一名志愿者
I need a volunteer.
洛佩兹吧
Yeah, Lopez.
坐这里
Right over here.
洛佩兹小姐  多谢你前来
Ms. Lopez, thank you for coming in.
我愿意帮助纽约警局
Anything I can do to help the NYPD.
昨晚发生了一起案件
Uh, so a crime was committed last night,
而你的名字被提到了
and your name was mentioned.
不知你可否告诉我你昨晚在哪
I was wondering if you could tell me where you were.
嗯  我去看了哈利拳击馆的比赛
Sure. I went to the fights over at Harry's Gym.
你一个人去的吗
You go alone?
不  高田  钱伯斯  戴克也去了
No. Takata, Chambers, Decker, we all went.
你喝酒了吗
You have anything to drink?
是的  喝了几杯
Yeah, we had a few drinks.
多少
How many?
我不记得了
I don't remember.
包里是什么
What's in the bag?
为什么问这个
Why?
不知道  你拿到桌上来了啊
I don't know. You put it on the table.
肯定有什么意义吧
It m-must mean something.
戴克  你来
Decker, take her place.
洛佩兹小姐说的是实话吗
Was Ms. Lopez telling the truth?
你昨晚出去了吗
Were you out last night?
是的
Yeah.
你们四个整晚都在一起吗
And were the four of you out together all night?
别看他们  看我
Don't look at them. Look at me.
你们四个昨晚整晚都在一起看比赛吗
Were the four of you together all night watching the fight?
不
No.
洛佩兹和高田提前离开了
Uh, Lopez and Takata left early.
我走时钱伯斯还在
Chambers was still there when I left,
当时最后一场马上要开始了
which was right before the last fight.
知道什么是PED吗
Do you know what a PED is?
知道  兴奋剂
Yeah. It's a performance enhancing drug.
钱伯斯  你来
Chambers, take Decker's place.
-钱伯斯  -钱伯斯
- Chambers! - Chambers!
你想往哪跑  学员
Where you running to, recruit?
你不想错过警监剩下的课吧
You don't want to miss the rest of the Captain's lecture, do you?
转过去
Turn over.
想多挣点学分吗
Ready to earn some extra credit?
我要叫律师
I want a lawyer.
你最好找个好的
Yeah, well, you better get a good one.
陪审团不喜欢杀警察的人
Juries don't like cop killers.
等等  你以为我杀了巴多
Wait. You think I popped Bardot?
我们在你寝室桌子里
We found a stack of identical cards
-找到了一堆一样的卡片  -律师
- in your dorm room desk. - Lawyer.
你恐吓巴多
You sent that to Bardot
因为他发现你在贩毒
because he found out that you were dealing drugs.
律师
Lawyer!
好啊
Fine.
你想赌一发吗
You want in on a bet?
-赌什么  -赌你
- On what? - On you.
你不配合
You're not cooperating,
所以我不再考虑保护性监禁了
so I'm taking protective custody off the table,
我们要赌等
and a bunch of us are wagering
犯人得知你是警察
on how long you're gonna last
你能撑多久
once the inmates find out that you're a cop.
我赌12小时以内
I'm guessing under 12 hours,
我现在觉得自己运气很好
and I'm feeling real lucky right now.
等等
Wait.
我可以做交易吗
Can I make a deal?
看情况  交待
Depends. Start talking.
巴多被杀之后
Look, the fights, they didn't let out
比赛才开始
until after Bardot was murdered.
有证人可以证明我当时在馆内
Witnesses can verify I was there.
那你为什么恐吓他
So why did you threaten him?
巴多被杀的早晨看到我的毒品了
Bardot caught me with my stash the morning he was killed.
我写字条
I sent the note
是想避免他告密
hoping to keep him from ratting me out,
但巴多毫不害怕
only Bardot wasn't intimidated.
但他提出了交易  五千块封口费
But he offered a deal... five grand for his silence.
他似乎急着要现金  我就付了钱
Apparently he was desperate for cash, so I paid up.
他打车去了城里
He flagged a cab to the city.
他为什么这么急着需要钱
And why did he need the money so urgently?
我也不知道
Beats me.
不行  这个回答我不满意
Nah, you're gonna have to do better than that.
我真不知道
I don't know!
如果有人知道的话  肯定是他女朋友
But if anyone does, it'd be his girlfriend.
好吧  他女朋友叫什么名字
Okay. Does this girlfriend have a name?
戴克学员
Recruit Officer Decker.
我以前不上课的时候也经常来这
I used to come here between classes, too.
我很喜欢加练
I always enjoyed the extra practice.
可惜的是  假人不会反抗
Except, a mannequin doesn't resist arrest.
我可以的  警监  谢了
I got it, Captain. Thanks.
让我见识见识
Show me.
-我能提个建议吗  -警监  我明白
- Can I make a suggestion? - Captain, okay, I got it.
闭上嘴  听我讲  学员
Shut up and listen, recruit.
你能学到点东西
You might actually learn something.
来吧  转过身去
Come on. Turn around.
你是女的  这是个优势
Now, the fact that you're a woman is an advantage,
尤其是相比于男人来说
especially over men.
女人的重心比较低  所以利用好这一点
We have a lower center of gravity, so use it.
把重心压在臀部
Drop into your hips
然后一过临界点就把他拉过来
and then pull him past the tipping point.
懂了吗  好的
Got it? Okay.
上半身过去了  剩下的也就过去了
Once the chest goes through, the rest will follow.
试一下吧
Try it?
来吧
All right.
很好  你学得很快
Good. You're a quick study.
谢谢  警监
Thanks, Captain.
我们找到凶器了
We got the murder weapon.
一个捡废品的在一个垃圾袋里发现的
A dumpster diver found it buried in a bag of garbage.
枪都擦干净了
The gun was wiped clean,
但是弹夹里的子弹没有被擦过
but not the rounds in the magazine.
看看吧
Check this out.
指纹跟巴多的相符
The prints are a match to Bardot's.
如果是巴多装的子弹
If Bardot loaded it,
那也一定是他从
then he had to have been the one
学院里偷出来的
who stole it from the Academy.
这么说他是被自己的枪射中的
So he was shot with his own gun?
问题是
Question is,
他当初为什么要把枪偷出来呢
what was he doing with it out there in the first place?
学院是个充满压力的地方
The Academy is a stressful place.
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
在这里你会有很大压力
Plenty of pressures here.
特别是一个小错误
Especially since one mistake
就会让你的整个警察生涯有污点
can put a stink on an entire cop career.
比如  跟另一个学员
Like, getting caught
太亲近  而被抓到现行
fraternizing with another recruit.
你要把我开除吗
Are you gonna have me booted?
不是
No.
但是我要求你
But I-I need you to be
从现在开始一五一十地交待
on the up-and-up with me from now on.
没问题
Of course.
你想知道什么都行
Anything you want to know.
巴多要挟钱伯斯要五千块钱
Officer Bardot leveraged Chambers for five grand.
很显然他急着要用那笔钱
Apparently he needed that money urgently.
你知道原因吗
Do you know why?
不  完全不知道
No. No clue.
我发誓
I swear.
说实话
Look, the truth is,
丹尼有事瞒着我
Danny was hiding something from me.
前几晚他经常晚上出去
He'd been going out at night the last few nights,
这完全不是他的性格
which was really unlike him.
之后他会溜进我的房间
He'd slip into my room late.
跟我说他是去跑步了
Said he'd been out for a midnight jog,
不过我知道他是骗我的
but, I mean, I knew that was total BS
因为他进来的时候
because when he came in,
一点也不累  也没出汗
he wasn't tired, he wasn't sweaty.
只是身上有一股烂鱼味
Just always smelled like rotten fish.
是吗
Really?
是的  很奇怪  我问过他
Yeah. It was weird. I asked him about it.
他说是跑步时不小心踩到垃圾了
He said he accidently stepped in garbage on his run.
可如果真是这样的话  那么
But if that was the case, then --
为什么他每天晚上身上都有烂鱼味呢
Why did he smell like rotten fish every night?
-吃甜辣虾吗  -哪来的
- Sweet and pungent shrimp? - Where from?
唐人街  在一家修电脑的
Chinatown, across the street
破烂小店街对面买的
from the back-alley computer repair shop
巴多在那家修理店里
where Bardot was dropped
竟然花了五千块钱
with five grand burning a hole in his pocket.
他花这么多钱干了什么
What was he doing there?
我给店主看了他的照片  他就不说话了
Owner refused to talk when I showed her his photo.
所以我就查了一下她
So I looked into her.
据说她在黑市上
Word is she deals in black market
卖软件和硬件
software and hardware.
巴多可能从她那买了些东西
Bardot may have bought something from her.
我想知道原因是什么
I wonder why.
把巴多的笔记本电脑给维克拉姆
Let's get Bardot's laptop to Vikram,
让他仔细查查
have him run a deeper search.
好的
All right.
戴克说的有关巴多鞋的事有进展了
Decker's tip on Bardot's shoes paid off.
实验室检出
The lab identified
他鞋底上有野生苏格兰鲑鱼的鱼鳞
wild Scottish salmon scales on the soles.
而只有三个鱼市进口了野生苏格兰鲑鱼
And only three fish markets import wild Scottish salmon.
那一家和犯罪现场在同一个社区
That's the same neighborhood as the crime scene.
很显然  巴多连续好几晚去了那里
And apparently, Bardot went there on consecutive nights.
我们去鱼市走访一下
We'll canvass the fish market,
看看能不能查出他去那做什么
see if we can figure out what he was up to.
好的
Okay.
你说得对
You were right.
我发现了我清除记忆的真实原因
I uncovered the real reason I had my memories erased,
很糟糕
and it's bad.
我在一年半以前就知道了洛克塞特了
I knew about LokSat a year and a half ago...
在你司法部同事被谋杀之前
before your A.G. team was murdered,
在维克拉姆找到你之前
before Vikram sought you out
以及在那些杀手出现之前
and the hit squads came gunning.
贝克特  这事在你之前就被我遇上了
Beckett, this was on me before it was on you.
你之前就知道洛克塞特了
You knew about LokSat?
所有的事
Everything?
包括他们跟布莱肯的联系
Including their connection to Bracken?
可你却选择忘记这一切  为什么
And you chose to forget this? Why?
原因你很清楚
For reasons you know all to well.
我当时是想保护你
I was trying to protect you.
谁会伤害我
From who?
你自己
From yourself.
警监
Hey, Captain.
我们发现了一些情况  你得来看看
We found something you need to see.
我马上就去
I'll be right there.
我需要时间消化一下
I need time to process this.
什么情况
What is it?
我们在街上的监控视频中发现了
Well, we found street-cam footage of Bardot
被害前的巴多
before he was killed.
这是巴多在他被杀前一个小时
This is Bardot an hour before he was murdered
正走过一个鱼市
walking past the fish market,
那家鱼市位于一家内衣批发商
which is right across the alley
所在的小巷子对面
from a lingerie wholesaler.
这是杰克·弗拉纳根已知的一处门面
It is a known front for Jack Flanagan,
又名幸运杰克
A.K.A. Lucky Jack.
他是狩猎点区的黑手党老大
He's the Mafia boss who runs Hunts Point.
巴多在狩猎点区长大的
Bardot grew up in Hunts Point.
看看这个
Check this out.
巴多联系的那家法律事务所
The law firm that Bardot contacted,
为杰克·弗拉纳根代理
they represent Jack Flanagan.
巴多通过第三方
Bardot was communicating
和弗拉纳根联络
to Flanagan through a third party
这样就不会被追踪到
so it couldn't be traced.
还有更好的  给她看
And it gets better. Show her.
我们的被害人和爱尔兰黑手党勾结
Our victim was in league with the Irish Mafia.
弗拉纳根一定是把巴多
Flanagan must have planted Bardot
安插在纽约警局做间谍
in the NYPD as his mole.
很可能他从巴多还是个孩子时
For all we know, he's been grooming Bardot
就开始栽培他
since he was a kid in the old neighborhood.
但我不明白的是如果巴多听命于弗拉纳根
What I don't get is if Bardot was working for Flanagan,
巴多为什么带一把枪去赴约
why did Bardot bring a gun to the meeting?
自卫
Protection.
奥蒂兹说巴多
Ortiz said that Bardot
想摆平一件事情
was looking' to set something right.
他后悔做弗拉纳根的间谍
He had second thoughts about being a mole for Flanagan.
然后弗拉纳根因此杀了他
And then Flanagan killed him for it.
我只是想保护你不受伤害
I was trying to protect you.
谁的伤害
From who?
你自己
From yourself.
巴多的电脑
Bardot's computer.
维克拉姆找到一个隐藏文件夹
Vikram found a hidden folder
里面有纽约警局关于弗拉纳根及其同伙的所有文件
that contains every NYPD file of Flanagan and his crew.
监控照片  监听录音  犯罪现场调查
Surveillance photos, wire taps, C.I.S --
弗拉纳根能够始终先警方一步
everything that Flanagan would need
所需的所有东西
to stay one step ahead of the police.
但是巴多是怎么入侵纽约警局的安全网络的
But how did Bardot hack into the NYPD's secure network?
那可是存在指定部门的电脑里
It's hardwired into select department computers.
包括马龙副局长
Including the computer
在学院办公室里的电脑
in Commissioner Malone's office at the Academy.
巴多一定是潜入马龙的办公室
Bardot must have snuck into Malone's office,
在上面用了便携式解码器
used a portable password cracker on it.
那就是他用从钱伯斯那敲诈来的5000美元
That's what he got at the black market
从黑市上买来的东西
with the five grand he squeezed out of Chambers.
弗拉纳根利用巴多来得到这些文件
Flanagan used Bardot to get these files.
他拿到手之后  就转而对付自己的间谍
After he got them, he turned on his own mole.
巴多一定是预料到会被出卖
Bardot must have seen the double-cross coming.
他拔出自己的枪  他们打了起来
He pulled his gun, they fought,
弗拉纳根占据了上风
Flanagan got the upper hand,
然后他开枪打中了巴多的背
then he shot Bardot in the back.
好了  我们来调查弗拉纳根
All right. Let's dig into Flanagan.
看我们能不能证实这些
See if we can corroborate this.
-你想让我们把他抓来  -不  还不用
- You want us to pick him up? - Nope. Not yet.
我要和幸运杰克面对面谈谈
I'm gonna have a sit-down with Lucky Jack,
看看我能不能让他松口
see if I can rattle his cage.
你否认巴多为你提供
So you deny that Bardot supplied you
机密的纽约警局文件
with confidential NYPD files?
当然  这有偏见
Absolutely, with prejudice.
那孩子来这里是为了
That kid came in here
找一份女士内衣销售员的工作
looking for a job as a lingerie salesman.
巴多曾经听命于你
Bardot was working for you...
而我会证明是你杀了他
...and I'm gonna prove that you killed him.
20年了
20 years.
你们这些人20年到这里来
20 years you guys have been coming in here
带着各种对老幸运杰克的指控
with all these accusations against ol' Lucky Jack.
你们的问题在于
Your problem is that none of you
没有一个人能找到后续证据
ever follow it up with the proof.
所以  除非你来这里
So, unless you're here
是为了你生命中某个特别的人
to buy a pair of crotchless panties
想买条开裆裤
for that special someone in your life,
我建议你拿上你的帽子和书
I suggest you grab your hat and your books,
然后滚出我的店
and you get the hell out of my store.
看  这就是为什么我知道我能打败你
See, that's how I know I'm gonna take you down.
骄兵必败
It's the cocky ones that are the easiest.
你太忙于自作聪明
You're so busy being clever,
根本注意不到快要引火烧身
you don't see the matchstick falling out of your pocket.
我会找到那根火柴
Well, I'm gonna find that matchstick,
然后用它把你烧成灰
and then I'm gonna burn you with it.
我们怎么又走到这步田地
How did we end up here again?
你说谎来保护我  我说谎来保护你
You lie to protect me, I lie to protect you.
我没准备大喊大叫
I'm not gonna yell..
或是指责什么
or throw around blame.
要知道  小说家乔治·桑
You know, the novelist George Sand --
顺便说一句她是女的
who was a woman, by the way --
曾经写过"说谎  就像许可证  有它的"
once wrote "Lying, like license, has its --"
卡塞尔  可不可以帮我个忙
Castle, can you do me a favor?
任何事
Anything.
不要说话
Stop talking.
如果我们不说话  我们要做什么
So, if we're not talking, what are we doing?
警监
Captain.
警监  看来杰克·弗拉纳根
Captain, looks like Jack Flanagan's reach
探入学院内部的手不止巴多一个
goes deeper inside the Academy than just Bardot.
你说什么
What are you talking about?
其中一个学员是用弗拉纳根的法律事务所
Well, one of the recruits went to college on a scholarship
创建的信托提供的奖学金上的学
awarded by a trust created by Flanagan's law firm.
那么这笔奖学金就是弗拉纳根自己提供的
Now, that scholarship was financed by Flanagan himself.
所以弗拉纳根在警察学院里有第二个间谍
So Flanagan has a second mole in the police academy?
谁
Who?
我不是他的间谍  丹尼也不是
I am not his mole, okay? Neither was Danny!
我们找到了那些他非法入侵
We found the police files that he hacked
然后交给弗拉纳根的警方文件
and then handed over to Flanagan.
不
Oh, no.
不  不  不
No, no, no.
丹尼一定是为了救我做了一笔交易
Danny must have made a deal in order to save me.
救你什么
Save you from what?
那个搞大我母亲肚子的男人
The man that knocked up my mother.
你是弗拉纳根的女儿
You're Flanagan's daughter.
一夜情并不能让他成为一个父亲
A one-night stand does not make him a parent.
只能让他成为一个捐精者
It makes him a donor.
你拿了他的脏钱
You took his blood money.
他和我母亲有个协议
He and my mother had an arrangement --
保守我父亲身份的秘密
staying quiet on my paternity
换取她的每月开销
in exchange for monthly payouts to her
和我的大学基金
and a college fund for me.
但仅此而已
But that was it.
那为什么巴多要救你
Then why did Bardot need to save you?
几周前
A few weeks ago,
弗拉纳根发现我进了学院
Flanagan found out that I joined the Academy.
他要求我做他的内线  他的间谍
He demanded that I be his inside woman -- his mole.
威胁如果我不这么做就"揭发"我是他的女儿
Threatened to "Out" me as his daughter if I didn't.
我的事业还没来得及开始就会被完全毁掉
Ruin my entire career before it even began.
因为没有警察会相信幸运杰克的孩子
'Cause no cop will ever trust Lucky Jack's kid.
我慌了
I panicked.
我最后向丹尼坦白
I ended up opening up to Danny.
是他开导了我
He was the one that talked me off the ledge,
告诉我弗拉纳根是在虚张声势
told me that Flanagan was bluffing.
我完全不知道他会代替我做内应
I had no idea that he was gonna offer himself up in my place.
我该怎么做  警监
What do I do, Captain?
你能做的只有一件事
There is only one move that you can make.
你想不想抓住杀死巴多的凶手
Do you want to arrest Bardot's killer?
扳倒弗拉纳根
Bring down Flanagan --
纽约警局做了二十年都没成功的事
something the NYPD hasn't done for 20 years?
你可能是弗拉纳根唯一愿意敞开心扉的对象
You're the one person Flanagan might open up to.
你需要带窃听器
You need to wear a wire.
好了  你遇到了麻烦  你该怎么说
All right, you get into trouble, what are you gonna say?
-戴克  -怎么了
- Decker. - What?
说暗号
Panic phrase.
"我真的想喝一杯
"I could really use a drink right now.
-你有威士忌吗"  -没错
- Do you have any Scotch?" - Exactly.
只要听到这句话  我们就冲进去
You say that, we're gonna rush in.
你会没事的
You're gonna be fine.
好的
Okay.
你真的觉得她准备好了  警监
You really think she's ready for this, Captain?
不是所有人都像你这样坚强
Not everybody's as strong as you.
如果弗拉纳根识破她  那就太糟了
I'd be damned if Flanagan makes her.
他朝她开枪的时候绝不会犹豫
He won't hesitate to put a bullet in her skull.
她能处理好的
She can handle this.
好了  加油  你可以的
Come on. Come on. You got it.
浪子回头了
The prodigal daughter returns. Well...
看到你我有点惊讶
You know, I am a bit surprised to see you,
毕竟我们上一次谈话的时候
considering the last time we spoke,
我记得你让我滚开来着
I think you told me to screw myself, right?
是什么风把你吹来了
Why am I blessed with your presence on this day, huh?
来啊  说话啊  孩子
Come on. Speak up, child.
没事的  慢慢来
You got it. Nice and slow.
说
Speak.
事情不一定要这样发展
You know, it didn't have to play out this way.
让我做你的内应是一件事
It was one thing to ask me to be your rat.
但我爱的人自愿代替我时另一回事...
But when the man I loved volunteered and delivered...
你为什么要杀丹尼
Why did you kill Danny?!
有一件事很有意思
You know, it's, uh -- it's funny.
你是这些天来的第二个站在这里
You're the second lady cop in as many days
指控我犯了这个罪的女警察
to stand there and accuse me of said crime.
有意思
Funny.
该死  她被识破了
Damn it. She's made.
他们会弄死她的  警监
They're gonna smoke her, Captain.
我不再害怕你了
I'm not afraid of you anymore.
她从哪里弄来的枪
Where the hell did she get a gun?
要么你承认自己杀了丹尼  要么我就杀了你
Now admit to killing Danny, or I will end you.
你男朋友的死与我无关
I had nothing to do with your boyfriend's murder.
你这个可悲的人能不能为自己的行为负责一次
For once in your miserable life, own up to what you did!
-我没说谎  -我不信
- I'm not lying! - I don't believe you.
-纽约警察  -警察
- NYPD! - Police!
戴克  看着我  我让你看着我
Decker, look at me. I said look at me!
你可以抓住他  但不是以这种方式
You can take him down, just not like this.
你和他不一样
You are not him.
放下枪
Put the gun down.
只要你说实话  我就放下枪
As soon as you start telling the truth.
警监  做点什么
Come on, Captain. Do something.
弗拉纳根  老实交代
Flanagan, start talking!
好吧
Okay.
你的男朋友还算有种
Your boyfriend, uh, has a set of balls on him.
他冲进来  让我放弃
I mean, he marches in here and tells me to back down.
你知道我做了什么
And you know what I do?
我说  "可以  但你要帮我个小忙"
I say, "Sure, but you got to do a little something for me."
好吗
Okay?
你男朋友明白了  我们握手成交了  完毕
Now, your boy comes through, we shake hands, and that's it.
那是谁杀了他
Then who killed him?
我不知道谁杀了他
I don't know who killed him.
他有提到过和谁有矛盾吗
Did he mention having problems with anyone?
没有  听着...
No. No, no. Look, um...
他走的时候  有辆车也开走了
When he left, this car started down the street.
有一瞬间
Now, for a minute,
我想他可能被人跟踪了
I thought maybe he was being tailed.
是一辆黑色的车
It was a -- a dark sedan.
就这么多了  就这么多  我发誓
Now, that's it. That's it. I swear.
你怎么看
What do you think?
他在说实话
He's telling the truth.
退下
Stand down.
瞧瞧
Well, look at that.
你比你以为的更加像我
You are more like me than you know.
你看起来糟透了
You are a hot mess.
你昨晚和贝克特的谈话看来很顺利
I take it that your talk with Beckett last night went well?
不是谈话  而更像是爱尔兰式的干预大会
Less of a discussion, more of an Irish intervention.
这么说  你们就坐在那里喝着威士忌
So you just sat around drinking whiskey
避免谈论这个话题
and avoiding the subject.
是的  但我看得出来她还是很生我气
Yes. But I can tell she's still upset with me.
她今天早上没叫醒我就离开了
She left this morning without waking me.
对此你准备怎么办
So, what do you plan on doing about that?
不怎么办
Nothing.
这是我今天听到过的最蠢的话
Well, that has to be the stupidest thing I've heard all day.
我内心有一丝小小的希望
I am holding onto the thin hope
希望贝克特能打心底里原谅我
that Beckett can find it in her heart to forgive me.
里克  拜托  别再没精打采回避问题了
Rick, come on. Stop moping about.
去做点什么  改变现状
Go do something about it.
什么  消除贝克特的记忆
What? Have Beckett's memory wiped?
不
No.
我们找到了洛克塞特
We track down LokSat.
我们在西海岸的探险有了不错的成果
Our west-coast adventure yielded fruit.
我们掌握了洛克赛特抵达洛杉矶的时间范围
We have a window of time in which LokSat arrived in L.A.
如果我们排查所有通过公开或私人的地区机场
If we scrub the identities of everyone who landed
落地人员的身份
in any area airport via public or private,
总有一天我们可以找到目标
then sooner or later we'll find our target.
你一声令下  我就可以开始
I can start now. Say the word.
我不会再在没有贝克特的情况下
I'm not making any more decisions
做任何有关洛克赛特的决定了
concerning LokSat without Beckett.
这是我今天听到过的最机智的话
Now that is the smartest thing I've heard all day!
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
好了  我再给你拿点阿司匹林
Okay, I'll get you more aspirin.
你不能放弃
You are not quitting.
我不适合做警察  警监
I'm unfit to be a cop, Captain.
如果你之前没有说服我...
If you hadn't talked me down back there --
我肯定就扣下扳机了
I had every intention of pulling that trigger.
但你没有
But you didn't.
你恢复了理智  你做了正确的决定
You regained your wits, you made the right decision,
这是最重要的
and that's what counts.
在我的职业生涯中  在某个时刻我想过辞职
There was a point in my career where I wanted to quit.
我失去了我是为了正确的理由成为警察的信念
I lost faith that I became a cop for the right reason.
你是怎么找回你的信念的
How'd you get your faith back?
一个叫做罗伊·蒙哥马利的人帮助了我
A man named Roy Montgomery helped me.
他曾是我的警监
He was my Captain.
他没有放弃我  我也不会放弃你
He didn't give up on me, and I am not giving up on you.
别让你父亲来决定你是什么样的人
So don't let your father define who you are.
我一生都在努力逃脱他的掌控
I have been trying to outrun him my entire life.
我受够了逃避
I'm tired of running.
我要回学院  清理出我的房间
I'm gonna head back to the Academy, clean out my room.
戴克要退学了
Decker's quitting.
好吧
Well...
事情总时让人失望
It's always disappointing.
这种事也时有发生
It happens.
不  有我在  不能让这种事发生在她这样的学院身上
No, not to recruits like her. Not on my watch.
莱恩  快看这个
Ryan, check this out.
弗拉纳根说的是实情
Flanagan was telling the truth.
监控录像拍到了这个
Street cam caught this.
巴多离开弗拉纳根的住处后被一辆黑色轿车跟着
Dark sedan that was following Bardot after he left Flanagan's.
看不清司机
Can't make out the driver, though.
但可以看清车牌
But you can make out the plate.
是注册在谁的名下
Who's this registered to?
是我们中的一员
It's one of ours.
属于警察学院的车辆调配
Issued to the Police Academy Motor Pool.
算了吧  贝克特
Oh, come on, Beckett.
她拿得到好成绩
Just because she's got good scores
这并不代表她就能当个好警察
doesn't mean she'll make a good cop.
在我所见到的所有学员中
I'd put her on the street
我会先派她出任务
before any of the other recruits I've met.
埃斯波  你查到什么了吗
Hey, Espo. What do you got?
好的  那辆车注册在谁的名下
Okay. Who's the car registered to?
好的  谢谢提供新的进展
Yeah. Thanks for the update.
一切都还顺利吗
Everything all right?
把武器放下  立刻
Put your weapon down. Now.
你疯了吗  贝克特  你在做什么
Have you lost your damn mind, Beckett? What are you doing?
该死的  奥蒂兹别惹出不必要的麻烦
Damn it, Ortiz, don't make this harder than it needs to be!
我知道你做了什么
I know what you did.
等等  你觉得是我杀了巴多吗
Wait, you think I killed Bardot?
你怀疑巴多在给弗拉纳根做事
You suspected that Bardot was working for Flanagan,
所以你跟踪了他
so you followed him.
当你发现他是卧底时  你就除了他
And then when you found out he was a mole, you took him out.
你从哪得来的消息
Where are you getting this?
我们查到了你的配车
We tracked your service vehicle.
我
I...
我已经很多天没用那辆车了
I haven't used that car for days.
我把车借给了
I lent it to--
快走
Come on!
别乱动  你还好吗
Don't move. You okay?
是你干的对吗  马龙
So it was you, Malone?!
为什么
Why?
为什么你没有把巴多移交给内务处
Why didn't you just turn Bardot over to I.A.?
我不能那样做
I couldn't!
他发现了一些东西
Not after what he found!
你的办公电脑
Your office computer.
当他潜入你的电脑时  他发现了些东西
He found something when he hacked into it.
我被他逮了个正着
Caught my hand in the cookie jar.
四十年来我保护着这个城市
40 years I protected this city.
而我获得的感恩呢...
And the thanks I got --
三段失败的婚姻还有数不清的债务
three busted marriages and a mountain of debt!
我只是把欠我的拿回来而已
I took what I was owed.
事情没必要变成现在这样
It doesn't have to end like this.
但事实就是如此
Actually, it does.
我来把他引走
I'm gonna draw him away.
收手吧  马龙
Just give up, Malone.
我的警探已经查到了你的身上
My detectives are onto you.
错  他们只是查到了奥蒂兹
No, they're onto Ortiz.
该死
Damn it.
你准备怎么做  马龙
So, what are you gonna do, Malone?
把我杀了然后嫁祸给奥蒂兹吗
Kill me and stage it like Ortiz did it?
然后说你杀了他是自我防卫吗
Say you shot him in self-defense?
安排得很好  是吗
Good plan, huh?
也许可以发给我一枚奖牌
Probably give me a medal.
抓到你了
Peek-a-boo.
警长  我还以为我们终于摆脱你了呢
Sarge, I thought we finally got rid of you.
要干掉我
Oh, it's gonna take more than a bullet
一颗子弹可不够
to put me down for the long dirt nap.
你最好快点痊愈
Well, you best heal up quick.
过几周就有一批新生要进来
Got a new batch of recruits coming in a few weeks.
好  警长
All right, Sarge.
我们先把你送离开这
We'll get you out of here.
医生  谢谢
Medic. Thanks.
你怎么样
Hey, how you holding up?
我们抓住了杀害丹尼的凶手
Well, we caught Danny's killer,
但"幸运杰克"弗拉纳根仍然逍遥法外
but Lucky Jack Flanagan's still free.
会有他落网的一天
Yeah, well, his time will come.
留在纽约警局  你能帮上忙
Stay with the NYPD, and you can help with that.
但如果你想单打独斗  肯定行不通
But you can't do this if you go it alone.
你到底想不想当警察
Do you want to be a cop or not?
想
Yes.
我接受不了了
I can't do this anymore.
很好  我也不行了
Good. Neither can I.
等等  你说的是什么
Wait, what are you talking about?
你说的是什么
What are you talking about?
-我先问的  -我第二个问的
- I asked first. - And I asked second.
所以你先回答  我再接着你回答
So you should answer first, and I'll answer second.
-卡塞尔  -好吧
- Castle. - O-Okay.
不能再对他的事袖手旁观了
I can't sit on the sidelines anymore
鉴于洛克塞特牵涉其中
where LokSat is concerned.
我...有人因此丢了性命
I -- People have lost their lives.
从某方面来说  我难辞其咎
And in a way, I am culpable.
我明白你是想保护我
And I know you are trying to protect me,
但我求你不要这样做了
but I'm begging you not to.
我希望能参与进来
I want in.
很好  因为我想要你的加入
Good, because I need you in.
现在这是我们共同的战斗了
This is our fight now.
好的
Okay.
好  有些事情你该知道
Okay, then there's something you should know.
我消失那段时间身上的神秘枪伤
That mystery bullet wound I got when I disappeared?
我在洛杉矶受到了枪击
I was shot in Los Angeles.
在我中枪前两个小时
Two hours before I took that bullet,
洛克塞特搭乘飞机到达了市里
LokSat came to town, arriving by plane.
好的  在洛杉矶地区
Uh, okay. There are three major airports
有三个主要的机场
along with dozens of private ones
还有很多私人机场
in the Los Angeles area.
就有成千上万人
We're talking tens of thousands of people.
但也许维克拉姆能缩小这个数字
But maybe Vikram can whittle that number down.
我们就是在大海捞针
We're looking for a needle in a stack of needles,
但洛克塞特就是那枚针
but LokSat is one of those needles.
你觉得呢  贝克特
What do you say, Beckett?
我们可以从那开始
It's a place to start.
不
No.
这才是开始
This is.